let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What extends in two dimensions",
    answer: "Plane",
    options: [
      "Line",
      "Plane",
      "Point.",
      "none of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "How do you denote the measurement of an angle ∠A?",
    answer: "m∠A",
    options: [
      "m∠A",
      "a∠A",
      "θ∠A",
      "none of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "True or False: We can classify triangles based on their angles and number of sides.",
    answer: "Always true",
    options: [
      "Always true",
      "False",
      "Sometimes true",
      "Insufficient data"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is the equation of a circle in standard form?",
    answer: "(x - h)² +(y - k)²  = r ",
    options: [
      "(x + h)² +(y - k)²  = r ",
      "(x - h)² +(y + k)²  = r ",
      "(x - h)² +(y - k)²  = r ",
      "(x + h)² +(y + k)²  = r "
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "A piecewise function is a function in which:",
    answer: "more than one formula is used to define the output.",
    options: [
      "the formula to define the function must equate to 1.",
      "the formula to define the output must equate to 0.",
      "only one formula is used to define the output.",
      "more than one formula is used to define the output."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What are the two formulas for semi-circular functions?",
    answer: "f(x) = √r²-x² and f(x)= -√r²-x²",
    options: [
      "f(x) = √r²-x² and f(x)= -√r²-x²",
      "f(x) = √r³-x³ and f(x)= -√r³-x³",
      "f(x) = √r²+x² and f(x)= -√r²+x²",
      "f(x) = √r³+x³ and f(x)= -√r³+x³"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "TRUE OR FALSE: All exponential functions have horizontal asymptotes. ",
    answer: "False for some expressions.",
    options: [
      "Absolutely true",
      "Ridiculously false ",
      "True for positive exponents ",
      "False for some expressions."
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What are the two formulas for semi-circular functions?",
    answer: "f(x)=√r^2-x^2 and f(x)=-√r^2-x^2",
    options: [
      "f(x)=√r^2-x^2 and f(x)=-√r^2-x^2",
      "f(x)=√r^3-x^3 and f(x)=-√r^3-x^3",
      "f(x)=√r^2+x^2 and f(x)=-√r^2+x^2 ",
      "f(x)=√r^2+x^2 and f(x)=-√r^2+x^2 "
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "These are the four properties when handling logarithmic functions EXCEPT:",
    answer: "Change of Exponent",
    options: [
      "Quotient Rule ",
      "Product Rule",
      "Change of Exponent",
      "Change of Base Formula "
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Fill in the blanks: There are ______ steps in writing logarithmic expressions as separate logarithms. ",
    answer: "3",
    options: [
      "3",
      "2",
      "5",
      "4"
    ]
  },

/*----------------------------------------------------*/

{
    numb: 11,
    question: "We say that two or more geometric figures ________ when they have at least one point in common",
    answer: "intersect",
    options: [
      "interact",
      "interchange",
      "intersect",
      "intangle"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 12,
    question: "The sides of congruent angles have _____ measurements.",
    answer: "equal",
    options: [
      "different",
      "even-numbered",
      "odd-numbered",
      "equal"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 13,
    question: "The equation of the circle in standard form whose center is at (−3, 1)and radius of √11 units is _____.",
    answer: "(x+3)² + (y+1)²  = 11",
    options: [
      "(x+3)² + (y+1)²  = 11",
      "(x+3)² -(y+1)²  = 11",
      "(x-3)² +(y+1)²  = 11",
      "(x+3)² +(y-1)²  = 11"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 14,
    question: "The circle with the equation (x-4)² +(y+3)²  = 25 ha a radius of  _______ units.",
    answer: "5",
    options: [
      "4",
      "6",
      "3",
      "5"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 15,
    question: "x + y + Dₓ + Eᵧ+ F = 0 is the equation of a circle in _________ form. ",
    answer: "General",
    options: [
      "Standard",
      "General",
      "Formal",
      "Congruent"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 16,
    question: "The domain of a piecewise function is the set of all _______ where the function is defined.",
    answer: "x-values",
    options: [
      "y-values",
      "x-intercepts",
      "asymptotes",
      "x-values"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 17,
    question: "Half-parabolas have the equations f(x) = √x and ________.",
    answer: "f(x) = −√x",
    options: [
      "-f(x) = √x",
      "f(x) = −√x",
      "f(x) = √-x",
      "-f(x) = −√x"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 18,
    question: "A logarithmic function is the _______ of an exponential function. ",
    answer: "c. inverse",
    options: [
      "a. parent",
      "b. product",
      "c. inverse",
      "d. transformation"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 19,
    question: "What transformation on Logarithmic Functions is in the form f (x)= b^x+ c ?",
    answer: "Vertical Shift",
    options: [
      "Horizontal Shift",
      "Reflection on the y",
      "Vertical Compression",
      "Vertical Shift"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 20,
    question: "TRUE or FALSE: In the equation  2^x+3 = 2^4, x = 2.",
    answer: "False",
    options: [
      "False",
      "True",
      "Sometimes True",
      "Sometimes False"
    ]
  },

/*----------------------------------------------------*/

{
    numb: 21,
    question: "Find the distance between points Y (−2,3) and Z (6, −2) using the distance formula.",
    answer: "9.43",
    options: [
      "9.43",
      "9.45",
      "9.40",
      "9.44"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 22,
    question: "Determine the coordinates of the midpoint between the points S(−1, 6) and T(4, −6).",
    answer: "(3/2, 0)",
    options: [
      "none of the above",
      "(-3/2, 0)",
      "(3/2, 0)",
      "(0, 3/2)"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 23,
    question: "Find the number of turning points in the graph of the polynomial function y = 0.00339x² + 0.00143x - 5.95 .",
    answer: "1",
    options: [
      "1",
      "22",
      "2",
      "4"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 24,
    question: "Determine the behavior of the graph of the rational function f(x)= x + 1 / x² + 2x - 3 ",
    answer: "Decreasing",
    options: [
      "Increasing",
      "Constant",
      "Decreasing",
      "Both A and C"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 25,
    question: "Solve for the vertical asymptote of the function  f(x)= 6 + (x + 1)(x - 2)(x + 3) / (x + 1)(x - 2).",
    answer: " x = -3 and x = 1",
    options: [
      "x = 1 ",
      " x = -3 and x = 1",
      "x = 3",
      "x = 3 and x = 1"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 26,
    question: "Find the domain of the square root function y= -3√x-2+1 .",
    answer: "[2, ∞)",
    options: [
      "[0, ∞)",
      "[-∞, 2)",
      "[-2, ∞)",
      "[2, ∞)"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 27,
    question: "If a circle has a radius of 6 and the center is at (0, 0), what is its equation in standard form? ",
    answer: "x^2 + y^2 = 6^2",
    options: [
      "x^2 + y^2 = 6^2",
      "(x-6)^2 + (y-6)^2 ",
      "x^2 + y^2 = 0",
      "(x-0)^2 + (y-0)^2 = 6^2 "
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 28,
    question: "In a graph, what does the x-intercept represent?",
    answer: "The point where the graph intersects the x-axis",
    options: [
      "The lowest point on the graph",
      "The highest point on the graph",
      "The point where the graph intersects the x-axis",
      "The point where the graph intersects the y-axis"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 29,
    question: "In a graph, what does the slope of a line represent?",
    answer: "The steepness of the line",
    options: [
      "The rate of change in the x-coordinate",
      "The rate of change in the y-coordinate",
      "The distance between two points",
      "The steepness of the line"
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 30,
    question: "Given the equation of a circle x^2 + y^2 - 4x + 6y - 12 = 0, determine the center and radius of the circle.",
    answer: "Center: (2, 3), Radius: 3",
    options: [
      "Center: (2, 3), Radius: 3",
      "Center: (2, 3), Radius: 5",
      "Center: (2, -3), Radius: 3",
      "Center: (2, -3), Radius: 5"
    ]
  },

]
